<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Ubuntu Software - Enterprise software development.</title>
    <link>www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Ubuntu Software - Enterprise software development.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2018 15:37:57 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Disease Tracking Project</title>
      <link>www.example.com/work/ecdc-disease-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/work/ecdc-disease-tracking/</guid>
      <description>The European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control (ECDC) is an independent agency of the European Union (EU) whose mission is to strengthen Europe&amp;rsquo;s defences against infectious diseases.
ECDC required a system for tracking disease reporting within the European Union, and to collaborate with the other CDC centers worldwide.
Highlights Security
  [LDAP] (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lightweight_Directory_Access_Protocol) based integration into their existing Security systems.
  Security review of the system to access risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ideas</title>
      <link>www.example.com/services/ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/services/ideas/</guid>
      <description>Helping you confront the unknown and move forward. So that you can experiment and move fast, we use technologies and practices that adapt as we go.
  Digital strategy &amp;amp; service design.
  Experience design.
  Lean product development.
  Portfolio design &amp;amp; management.
  Customer research &amp;amp; testing.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modern Hospital Software</title>
      <link>www.example.com/work/modern-hospital/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/work/modern-hospital/</guid>
      <description>Patients, Doctors, Hospitals and Researchers all connected in real time to maximise health outcomes.
Connect Legacy systems with new emerging standards like [FHIR] (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fast_Healthcare_Interoperability_Resources), allowing the old systems to be brought into Modern Software practices.
The platform, called Afira, is designed for the Medical / Health sector and going through beta testing now. We are currently working with the Germany Ministry of Health and other government and standards bodies.
We are currently looking for new partners that wish to leverage the system, so feel free to contact us for a chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BG Group gas project</title>
      <link>www.example.com/work/bg-group-gas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/work/bg-group-gas/</guid>
      <description>BG Group plc was a British multinational oil and gas company headquartered in Reading, United Kingdom, with operations in 25 countries across Africa, Asia, Australasia, Europe, North America and South America.
They required a real time Trading Portal for the spot price gas market with a back-office system to track the gas production sites and feed into their reporting division.
Highlights GUI
  Trading portal with dynamic real time updates running on large format Screens in the Trading Hall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Syngenta agro-chemical project</title>
      <link>www.example.com/work/syngenta-agro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/work/syngenta-agro/</guid>
      <description>Syngenta is a global business operating in the agro-chemical sector, with its headquarters in Switzerland. It produces and sells crop protection products, seeds, and products for lawn and gardens. It is active on a vertically-integrated basis in the research, development, manufacture and marketing of a wide range of crop protection products and seeds.
They required a system to track experimental research. This required bridging legacy and new systems in a continuous streaming platform whereby all systems push updates into the other systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>www.example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>History</title>
      <link>www.example.com/history/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 09:29:16 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/history/</guid>
      <description>About Heading </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Innovate</title>
      <link>www.example.com/services/innovate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/services/innovate/</guid>
      <description>Technology increasingly is the business. Disrupt yourself or be disrupted. For over 20 years we have been helping our clients think bigger and deliver better.
  Agile delivery leadership.
  Lean Enterprise/ Lean organisation.
  Organisational transformation.
  Rapid prototyping.
  Innovation labs.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Systems Advisory</title>
      <link>www.example.com/services/tech-advisory/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.example.com/services/tech-advisory/</guid>
      <description>Often projects need external advice and workshops to help them in various ways. Systems architecture is one of the most valuable things a team can have if they are not sure what approach they need.
Team coaching This can help the techncial team to learn established patterns and practices to make the techncial aspects run smoother and lower risks and time.
Business goal analysis Each project is different and often has a goal in general but needs help in refining those goals from the business perspective into tangible technical architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>